Guide to the New York Foundation For the Arts (NYFA) Records MSS.515
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series VIII. Other NYFA Programs, 1970-2010; 45 linear feet in 45 record cartons
  - Subseries J. Arts and Technology, 1995-2002; 9 linear feet
    - Arts and Cultural Council for Greater Rochester, 2001 (Box 45, Folder 74)
    - Arts Council for Chautauqua County, Inc., 2001 (Box 45, Folder 75)
    - Arts Horizons, Inc., 2001 (Box 45, Folder 76)
    - Carneie Art Center/Tonowandas' Council on the Arts, 2001 (Box 45, Folder 77)
    - Chenango County Council of the Arts, 2001 (Box 45, Folder 78)
    - City Lore, Inc., 2001 (Box 45, Folder 79)
    - CITYarts, Inc., 2001 (Box 45, Folder 80)
    - Community Arts Partnership of Tompkins County, 2001 (Box 45, Folder 81)
    - Council on the Arts and Humanities for Staten Island, 2001 (Box 45, Folder 82)
    - Dahesh Museum of Art, 2001 (Box 45, Folder 83)
    - Dance Space Center, 2001 (Box 45, Folder 84)
    - DanceWorks, Inc. (Pentacle), 2001 (Box 45, Folder 85)
    - David Parker and the Bang Group, 2001 (Box 45, Folder 86)
    - Davka Sephardic Dances, 2001 (Box 45, Folder 87)
    - Drunken Boat, 2001 (Box 45, Folder 88)
    - Edward Hopper Preservation Foundation, 2001 (Box 45, Folder 89)
    - En Foco, Inc., 2001 (Box 45, Folder 90)
    - Essex Community Heritage Organization, Inc., 2001 (Box 45, Folder 91)
    - Exit Art/The First World, Inc., 2001 (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - Freudig Singers of Western New York, 2001 (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - Heritage Foundation of Oswego, Inc., 2001 (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - High 5 Tickets to the Arts, Inc., 2001 (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - Home for Contemporary Theatre and Art DBA HERE, 2001 (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - House Foundation for the Arts, 2001 (Box 46, Folder 6)
    - The Hudson Review, 2001 (Box 46, Folder 7)
    - Inkwell Magazine, 2001 (Box 46, Folder 8)
    - Inta, Inc. (Eiko and Koma), 2001 (Box 46, Folder 9)
    - J. Mandle Performance, Inc., 2001 (Box 46, Folder 10)
    - JCC of Mid-Westchester, 2001 (Box 46, Folder 11)
    - La MaMa Experimental Theatre Club, Inc., 2001 (Box 46, Folder 12)
    - Lower Adirondack Regional Arts Council (LARAC), 2001 (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - Lower East Side Tenement Museum, 2001 (Box 46, Folder 14)
    - Lower Manhattan Cultural Council, 2001 (Box 46, Folder 15)
    - Manhattan Class Company (MCC Theater), 2001 (Box 46, Folder 16)
    - Memorial Art Gallery of the University of Rochester, 2001 (Box 46, Folder 17)
    - Mint Theater Company, 2001 (Box 46, Folder 18)
    - New York State Alliance for Arts Education, 2001 (Box 46, Folder 19)
    - Open City, Inc., 2001 (Box 46, Folder 20)
    - Poets and Writers, Inc., 2001 (Box 46, Folder 21)
    - Pregones Theater, 2001 (Box 46, Folder 22)
    - Racing Thoughts, Inc. aka Jane Comfort and Company, 2001 (Box 46, Folder 23)
    - Rattapallax Press, 2001 (Box 46, Folder 24)
    - Rhizome.org, 2001 (Box 46, Folder 25)
    - Roulette Intermedium, Inc., 2001 (Box 46, Folder 26)
    - Roxbury Arts Group, Inc., 2001 (Box 46, Folder 27)
    - Schenectady Museum, 2001 (Box 46, Folder 28)
    - Sculpture Center, Inc., 2001 (Box 46, Folder 29)
    - Soho Think Tank, 2001 (Box 46, Folder 30)
    - South Bristol Cultural Center, 2001 (Box 46, Folder 31)
    - Staret, The Directors Company, 2001 (Box 46, Folder 32)
    - Staten Island Institute of Arts and Sciences, 2001 (Box 46, Folder 33)
    - The Builders Association, 2001 (Box 46, Folder 34)
    - The East End Special Players, 2001 (Box 46, Folder 35)
    - The Field (Peformance Zone, Inc.), 2001 (Box 46, Folder 36)
    - The New York Collegium, 2001 (Box 46, Folder 37)
    - The Pearl Theatre Company, Inc., 2001 (Box 46, Folder 38)
    - The Rotunda Gallery, 2001 (Box 46, Folder 39)
    - The Open Eye Theater, 2001 (Box 46, Folder 40)
    - Tappan Zee Dance Group, 2001 (Box 46, Folder 41)
    - Tioga County Council on the Arts, 2001 (Box 46, Folder 42)
    - Trisha Brown Dance Company, 2001 (Box 46, Folder 43)
    - TV Dinner Project, 2001 (Box 46, Folder 44)
    - WaxFactory, 2001 (Box 46, Folder 45)
    - White Pine Press, 2001 (Box 46, Folder 46)
    - Whitney Museum of American Art, 2001 (Box 46, Folder 47)
    - Women's Studio Workshop, 2001 (Box 46, Folder 48)
    - The Early Music Foundation, Inc., 2001 (Box 46, Folder 49)
    - The Writers Room, 2001 (Box 46, Folder 50)
    - TechTAP Applicant History and Recipients, 2000-2001 (Box 46, Folder 51)
    - Alleyway Theatre, Inc., 2000-2001 (Box 46, Folder 52)
    - Ballet Artists of WNY dba Neglia Ballet Artists, 2000-2001 (Box 46, Folder 53)
    - Big Orbit Gallery, 2000-2001 (Box 46, Folder 54)
    - Locust Street Neighborhood Art Classes, 2000-2001 (Box 46, Folder 55)
    - LKPainter Community Center, 2000-2001 (Box 46, Folder 56)
    - Community Music School, 2000-2001 (Box 46, Folder 57)
    - Explore and More... A Children's Museum, 2000-2001 (Box 46, Folder 58)
    - Squeaky Wheel, 2000-2001 (Box 46, Folder 59)
    - Expenses for Buffalo Knowledge in Technology (KIT) Program, 2001 (Box 46, Folder 60)
    - Knowledge in Technology (KIT): Washington DC Cycle, Expenses, 2001-2002 (Box 46, Folder 61)